<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--

    contains all the hotels text displayed

    - Title Text
    - SubText (next to the rating)
    - Body Text
    - Address Text
    - Detailed Description Text
-->
<resources>
    <string-array name="location_hotel_titles">
        <item>Park Hyatt</item>
        <item>Hotel Imperial</item>
        <item>Palais Coburg Residence</item>
        <item>Hilton Vienna</item>
        <item>Arcotel Wimberger</item>
        <item>Star Inn Hotel</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="location_hotel_subtext">
        <item>5-Star Hotel</item>
        <item>5-Star Hotel</item>
        <item>5-Star Hotel</item>
        <item>4-Star Hotel</item>
        <item>4-Star Hotel</item>
        <item>3-Star Hotel</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="location_hotel_bodytext">
        <item>1900s hotel with a luxe spa, an indoor pool &amp; refined dining.</item>
        <item>Upscale quarters in a grand, 19th-century hotel.</item>
        <item>Opulent lodging in a 19th-century palace.</item>
        <item>Upscale rooms in a refined hotel.</item>
        <item>Chic colonial hotel with an elegant restaurant.</item>
        <item>Polished hotel in a contemporary building.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="location_hotel_adresses">
        <item>Am Hof 2, 1010 Wien</item>
        <item>Kärntner Ring 16, 1015 Wien</item>
        <item>Coburgbastei 4, 1010 Wien</item>
        <item>Am Stadtpark 1, 1030 Wien</item>
        <item>Neubaugürtel 34 &#8211; 36, 1070 Wien</item>
        <item>Linke Wienzeile 224, 1150 Wien</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="location_hotel_desc">
        <item>
            This lavish hotel in an early 20th-century former bank is a 6-minute walk from Hofburg Imperial Palace and a 7-minute walk from St. Stephen\'s Cathedral.
            \n\nThe plush rooms and suites mix contemporary with traditional Viennese decor, and feature free Wi-Fi and coffeemakers, along with flat-screen TVs, minibars and designer toiletries. Suites add separate living areas. Room service is available.\n\n
            Amenities include a palatial restaurant, a ritzy cocktail bar and an elegant, wood-paneled whisky/cigar lounge. The luxe spa has a heated indoor pool and a fitness center, and there\'s also a refined tea room and a business center. Parking is available (fee).
        </item>
        <item>
            In a grand building dating from 1863, this venerable, luxury hotel, with a refined, old-world vibe, is 13 minutes\' walk from Hofburg Palace.
            \n\nFeaturing chandeliers, antiques and marble bathrooms, the elegant rooms come with TVs and limited free Wi-Fi. Suites add opulent decor, and most offer butler service; some include balconies, whirlpool tubs and complimentary minibars.
            \n\nThere\'s a sophisticated restaurant, and a posh piano bar featuring classical music and live performances, as well as a casual cafe offering champagne breakfast. Other amenities include a gym and parking (fee).
        </item>
        <item>
            This opulent all-suite hotel in a 19th-century palace is 6 minutes\' walk from the medieval St. Stephen\'s Cathedral and an 11-minute walk from the Vienna State Opera.
            \n\nElegant suites with garden or cathedral views feature kitchenettes, antique furnishings, free Wi-Fi and flat-screen TVs. Some suites offer separate living spaces, rooftop terraces, whirlpool tubs and/or saunas. Upgraded suites have 2 levels. Room service is available.
            \n\nBreakfast is complimentary. There\'s a chic fine-dining restaurant and a glass-enclosed eatery with a terrace. Other amenities include a wine bar, 6 wine cellars and a luxe spa with an indoor pool and a hot tub.
        </item>
        <item>
            This polished hotel is a 1-minute walk from an S-Bahn station, an 11-minute stroll from St. Stephen\'s Cathedral and 1.1 km from the Musikverein Wien concert hall.
            \n\nThe upscale rooms come with Wi-Fi (fee), flat-screens, minibars, coffeemakers and desks. Some rooms have city or cathedral views. Executive rooms add access to a private lounge serving breakfast and drinks at no cost. Suites add living areas; some feature balconies and kitchens. Room service is available.
            \n\nThe hotel offers a chic European restaurant and a modern bar. Other amenities include a fitness room, a sauna and a steam room, plus a business center and 17 event rooms.
        </item>
        <item>
            A 6-minute walk from both Wien Westbahnhof train station and Wiener Stadthalle event center, this refined brick and glass hotel dating from 1871 is 2.6 km from Hofberg Imperial Palace.
            \n\nThe relaxed rooms feature free Wi-Fi, flat-screens and minibars. Suites add separate living areas and upgraded suites have city views. Room service is available.
            \n\nAmenities include an upscale Viennese restaurant serving a breakfast buffet, weekly jazz buffet (fees), and a vegan menu. There\'s a colonial-style bar, and a spa with saunas, whirlpools and a gym. A business center is available, and there are meeting rooms and conference facilities for up to 970 people.
        </item>
        <item>
            This casual hotel is a minute\'s walk from an U-bahn station, 1.8 km from the baroque Schönbrunn Palace and 3.2 km from downtown Vienna.
            \n\nThe unfussy rooms are decorated with classic wood furnishings, and come with desks, complimentary Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and minifridges. Upgraded rooms feature leather sofas; suites add separate living areas. Kids 10 and under stay free with an adult.
            \n\nThere\'s an informal 24-hour lobby bar. A breakfast buffet and parking are available for extra fees.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>